streamnation.com 2015-03-22

# StreamNation | Your Video Collection Anywhere & Everywhere

Welcome to StreamNation! Protecting your privacy is really important to us. Accordingly, we’re providing this Privacy Policy to explain our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that we receive when you use our Services (as defined in our Terms of Service, accessible at [www.streamnation.com/tos](http://www.streamnation.com/tos)). This Privacy Policy applies only to those websites, services, software and mobile applications included within “Services” and doesn’t apply to any third-party websites, services, software or mobile applications, even if they are accessible through our Services. Also, please note that, unless we define a term in this Privacy Policy, all capitalized words used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service. 

By accepting this Privacy Policy, you hereby enter into an agreement made between you and The Digital Nation, a Luxembourg limited liability company (société à responsabilité limitée) existing under the laws of Luxembourg, having its registered address at 117, avenue Gaston Diderich, L-1420Luxembourg and registered with the Luxembourg register of Commerce and Companies under number B 177.564, and having a share capital of EUR 12,400. Digital Nation S.à r.l., together with its parent, subsidiaries and affiliates are collectively referred to herein as "DN", “we”, “our” or “us”. 

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THE SITE. BY USING THE SITE, YOU EXPLICITLY ACCEPT THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD LEAVE THE SITE IMMEDIATELY AND CEASE ALL YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES. 

## How do we collect and use information?

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services, to administer your use of the Services (including your Account, if you are an Account holder), and to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate our Services. 

DN uses your personal information to provide you with a superior customer experience and, as necessary, to administer our business. We use your personal information for, inter alia, the following purposes: 

• Provide you with services and information, through e-mails from DN, the Site, your electronic devices, Apps and Software; 

• Provide customer service; 

• Conduct research and perform analysis in order to measure, maintain, protect, develop and improve our Services; 

• Administer sweepstakes, contests, promotions or surveys and provide appropriate notifications; 

• Communicate with you about special offers, events, or new products or services that may be of interest to you; 

• Customize and enhance the Services; 

• Make communications necessary to notify you regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues; and 

• Manage our business. 

## Clarity

We strive to communicate clearly about your privacy and how we handle your personal information. 

## Security

We follow security standards, processes and procedures that are designed to protect your personal information. 

## Integrity

We do not sell or rent your personal information and respect your preferences with respect to your personal information. 

## What is the personal information that we collect?

When you create an Account we’ll collect certain information that can be used to identify you (“Personally Identifiable Information” or “PII”), such as your email address, username and password. If you purchase a subscription to use the Services, we (or our third party payment processor e.g. PayPal ®) may also collect billing information such as your credit card information and billing address. 

### Your User Content

We collect and store the User Content you upload, stream or access via the Services. 

### Information Collected Using Cookies.

We collect certain information through the use of “cookies,” which are small text files that are saved by your browser when you access our Services. Cookies help us to: (1) speed navigation; (2) remember information you gave us so that you do not have to re-enter it; and (3) monitor the total number of visitors, pages viewed, and the total number of banners displayed. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to identify that you’ve logged in to the Services and to tell us how and when you interact with our Services. We may also use cookies to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on our Services and to customize and improve our Services. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted when you log off from the Services and close your browser. Although most browsers automatically accept cookies, you can change your browser options to stop automatically accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies. Please note, however, that if you don’t accept cookies, you may not be able to access all portions or features of the Services. Some third-party services providers that we engage may also place their own cookies on your browser. Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of cookies and does not include use of cookies by such third parties. 

### Information Related to Use of the Services.

Our servers automatically record certain information about how a person uses our Services (we refer to this information as “Log Data”), including both Account holders and non-Account holders (either, a “User”). Log Data may include information such as a User’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, links on our Services that a User clicked on, duration of use of the Services, Content playback time, the amount of storage used in a User’s Account, the amount of Content a User accesses via the Services, the number of times our Services are used and other statistics. We use this information to administer the Services and we analyze (and may engage third parties to analyze) this information to improve and enhance the Services by expanding their features and functionality and tailoring them to our Users’ needs and preferences. We may use a person’s IP address to fight spam, malware and identity theft. We also use the IP address to generate aggregate, non-identifying information about how our Services are used. 

We use service providers such as Google Analytics and Mixpanel to collect, monitor and analyze this information in order to increase our Services’ functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor our Services to our visitors’ needs. We also use this information to verify that visitors to our Site and our mobile applications meet the criteria required to process their requests. Accordingly, Log Data is shared with Google and Mixpanel, which have their own privacy policies (accessible at [www.google.com/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and <https://mixpanel.com/privacy/>, respectively) addressing how each party uses such information. 

### Location Information.

When you use our App we collect and store information about where you are located, such as by converting your IP address into a rough geolocation. 

Most of mobile devices allow you to switch off the geolocation feature. If you do not wish that data regarding your location be collected, stored and processed by DN, you should modify the personal settings of your mobile device. 

##  BY DOING BUSINESS WITH OR INTERACTING WITH DN, YOU CONSENT TO THE USE OF THE TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES AS DESCRIBED ABOVE. 

### Inviting Friends to use the Services or Access User Content.

Account holders can invite their friends to use the Services via their Accounts in connection with our Referral Program. Account holders can also send invitations to their friends to obtain access to User Content collections. In connection with these features of the Services, Account holders may connect their Accounts with their accounts with certain third-party services such as Facebook (each, a “Third Party Account”) to enable Account holders to contact their friends and contacts via such Third Party Accounts. If an Account holder chooses to connect with a Third Party Account via the Services, the Account holder may have to provide us with his or her username (or userID) so that his or her identity can be authenticated by the Third Party Account. When the authentication is complete, we’ll be able to access certain information such as lists of Third Party Account friends or contacts and other information that the Account holder’s privacy settings on the Third Party Account permit us to access in order to present such friends or contacts to the Account holder via the Services, as applicable. We don’t receive or store passwords for any Third Party Accounts. Alternatively, if an Account holder provides DN with the email address of a friend, a message will be sent from DN to such friend on the applicable Account holders’ behalf, inviting the friend to use the Services.  These email addresses will be used only for the purpose of sending the one-time communication to the friends and for analyzing the success of this feature of the Services. Invited friends may request that DN delete their PII by contacting us at theteam@streamnation.com. In any case, after 6 months, email addresses of friends who have not created an Account will be automatically deleted from our system. 

## What Information Do We Share With Third Parties?

We will not share any PII that we have collected from you except as described in this Policy:

### Your Use of the Services.

The Services provide features that allow other Account holders to access your User Content and consequently, if you choose to utilize these features, other Account holders will have access to such User Content in accordance with the selections you make via the Services and the permitted functionality of the Services. Such User Content will be accessible in connection with your Account user name. 

### Information Shared with Our Services Providers.

We may engage third party service providers to work with us to administer and provide the Services. These third-party services providers have access to your PII only for the purpose of performing services on our behalf, can only process your personal information upon express request from us and are expressly obligated not to disclose or use your PII for any other purpose. 

### Information Shared with Third Parties.

We may share aggregated information and non-identifying information with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other similar purposes. DN do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. 

### Information Disclosed in Connection with Business Transactions.

Information that we collect from our users, including PII, is considered to be a business asset. As a result, you agree that if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy or if we are acquired as a result of a transaction such as a merger, acquisition or asset sale or part of a restructuring or a reorganization, your PII may be disclosed to the entities and advisors involved subject to a confidentiality agreement and may also be transferred as part of such sale, restructuring, reorganization, bankruptcy, merger or similar event.. 

### Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others.

It is our policy to protect you from having your privacy violated through abuse of the legal systems, whether by individuals, entities or government, and to contest claims that we believe to be invalid under applicable law. However, it is also our policy to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties. Accordingly, we reserve the right to disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary: (i) to satisfy or comply with any applicable law, regulation or legal process or to respond to lawful requests, including subpoenas, warrants or court orders; (ii) to protect our property, rights and safety and the rights, property and safety of third parties or the public in general; and (iii) to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. 

## The Security of Your Information

We take significant and appropriate measures to protect the information that we collect from or about you (including your PII) from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. While we are focused on the security of your personal information and follow strict standards, processes and procedures that are designed to protect your personal information, you must remember that the Internet is a global communications vehicle open to threats, viruses and intrusions from others and so we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that we will be able to protect your personal information at all times and in all circumstances. 

## Links to Other Sites

Our Services may contain links to other websites and services. Any information that you provide on or to a third-party website or service is provided directly to the owner of the website or service and is subject to that party's privacy policy. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to such websites or services and we’re not responsible for the content, privacy or security practices and policies of those websites or services. To protect your information we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of other websites and services that you access. 

## Modifying Your Information

You can access at reasonable intervals and at no charge the PII we process, the purpose of the processing, the categories of personal information we process as well as the third parties to whom your PII may be communicated. You have the right to ask us not to use your PII for direct marketing purposes. 

You have the right (i) to oppose, at any moment, for personal legitimate and primordial reasons, to the processing of your PII; (ii) to oppose, upon request and at no charge, to the processing of your PII for prospecting purposes and (iii) to be informed prior to any communication of your PII to a third party for prospecting purposes and to oppose (at no charge) to the communication of your PII to such third party. 

In case of incomplete or inaccurate PII, you have the right to ask us to modify or delete your PII and your Account, in that case, please contact us at theteam@streamnation.com with your request. We’ll take steps to delete your information as soon as is practicable, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law. 

## International Transfer

You acknowledge and hereby explicitly agree that your PII may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you’re located outside of Luxembourg and choose to provide your PII to us, we may transfer your PII to Luxembourg and process it there. 

## Our Policy Toward Children

DN is committed to complying with all applicable laws and regulations regarding the collection, storage and use of PII of Minors. 

Except as noted below: (i) our services are marketed for and directed towards purchase by adults or with the consent of adults; (ii) Individuals under the age of 18 ("Minors") are not permitted to use the Services without the supervision of a parent or legal guardian; (iii) we do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from children under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to register for an online account or to post personal information on the Site; and (iv) should we learn that someone under the age of 18 has provided any personal information to or on any of the Site, we will remove that information as soon as possible. 

## Changes to Privacy Policy

Any information that we collect is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may, however, modify and revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy, we’ll notify you of such changes by posting them on the Services or by sending you an email or other notification, and we’ll indicate when such changes will become effective. 

## Dispute

Any dispute between you and us regarding the privacy of your personal information is subject to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service, including limitation on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the Grand Duchy of Luxembourg. 

## Notices

Any notices or other communications provided by DN under this Privacy Policy, including those regarding modifications to this Privacy Policy, will be given by DN: (i) via email; or (ii) by posting to the Services. For notices made by e-mail, the date of receipt will be deemed the date on which such notice is transmitted. You hereby consent to receive electronic notices from us, whether addressed to the email address associated with your Account or another email address that you provide to us. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable local law, you acknowledge and agree that any communication via email or by postings to the Services satisfies any legal requirement that such communications be made in writing. You may give notice to us via email to the following address: [theteam@streamnation.com](mailto:theteam@streamnation.com)

## Questions?

Please contact us at [theteam@streamnation.com](mailto:theteam@streamnation.com) if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy.
